# http://BenMerchant.dev

## Full Stack JavaScript Developer

benjaminmerchant@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

With thirteen years of experience, arguably one of the best servers in this town. The ability comes from passion, dedication, and appreciation for the job. Also helps to be naturally geared to be good at it; personable, extroverted. Looking forward to beginning and mastering a new career path.

### **EDUCATION**

### BridgeValley CTC, South Charleston, WV

AAS Computer Science Technology: Software Development

Graduation: December 2018

Topics Covered: JavaScript, C#, ASP.net, Python,

MySQL, PHP, Database Management, Algorithms

Self-taught capstone course: (Node.is, MongoDB, AngularJS) =>

http://startpos.management : all-in-one restaurant CMS

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Bricks & Barrels - Server/Bartender

2016 - Present

- Provided superior service to guests
- Maintain restaurant website bricksnbarrels.com (WordPress)

SuTei Asian Cuisine - Assistant Manager

2013 - 2015

- Trained new bartenders and created new menu items
- Handled day-to-day operations while manager built a new restaurant

Bluegrass Kitchen - Server/Brunch Manager

2011-2012

- Managed the bar for weekend brunch and weekday lunch
- Provided excellent service to guests